Satheesh Aakula () Featured

Application Programmer seeking roles in Software Development, Database Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, Performance Tuning, Technology Management, Technical Architecture, Software Testing, Quality Analysis, Oracle, SQL, PLSQL



Current Designation: Application Programmer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Current Company: black knight financial service Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: Banking/Financial Services/Broking

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Application Programmer, Software Developer, Software Development, Database Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, Performance Tuning, Technology Management, Software Testing, Quality

Analysis, Oracle, SQL, PLSQL, Unix

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Having 5.8 years of experience in the IT industry as a Software Developer.

Hands on experience in Oracle SQL & PL/SQL.

Hands on experience in Oracle Forms.

Good working knowledge on Oracle SQL Developer & TOAD.

Hands on experience in loading data to Database using SQL * Loader.

Knowledge on TOAD Data Modeler.

Knowledge on Core Java, Tableau, Oracle Data Integrator

Strong communication, collaboration & team building skills with proficiency at grasping new technical concepts quickly & utilize the same in a productive manner.

Work Experience

black knight financial service as Application Programmer Oct 2016 to Till Date

Having 5+ years of relevant experience in software development and implementation and has expertise in the writing of SQL, PL/SQL, and Code.

Black Knight Financial Services as Application Programmer

Oct 2016 to Dec 2016

Black Knight Financial Services as Application Programmer

Oct 2016 to Dec 2020

Worked as PI/sql Developer

Black Knight Financial Services Pvt. Ltd as Application Programmer Oct 2016 to Dec 2020

Oct 2016 to Dec 2020

Worked as a PL/SQL Developer.

Temenos Multifonds India Pvt. Ltd as Software Developer

Jan 2015 to Sep 2016

Worked as PL/SQL Developer

Education

UG: B.Sc (Chemistry) from Andhra University in 2006

PG: MCA (Computers) from University of Mysore in 2010

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
SQL, PL/SQL, Oracle 12c	
Oracle SQL Developer, TOAD	
ORACLE REPORTS	
Tortoise SVN, Tortoise GIT	
MS OFFICE	
WINDOWS	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Telugu				
Kannada				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time